So, friends, I
welcome you all to
my YouTube channel, which is called
Kuber Marathi. So, friends, in this
video, we are going to discuss
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company. So, friends, this company is
a general insurance company and it is
a subsidiary of ICICI.
Friends, the company is
very
active in general insurance. It works in the general insurance sector.
And finally, its
results for the third quarter, that is, the December quarter, have been announced.
So, now let's discuss, friends,
what could be the next target in the stock after the results of this quarter?
So, definitely, after these
quarterly results,
we
saw an average intraday rise of 2.47%.
We have seen a good momentum here.
So, now let's discuss,
friends,
what new
targets will the stock have in the coming days?  You can see now
in the long term, friends, you
can see that so far, friends, there are 187% returns.
Friends, IPO came here in 2017.
Here, IPO has
given us almost all the money that is there, it is the money of the
investors. Friends, 200%
returns have been
given on the money of the investors. That means that all the money that is there has almost
tripled.
Now, you can see, friends,
we have seen a 247% rise in intraday. We have seen a
4.47
% rise in five days. We have seen a little bit of a
3% rise in a month.
And we have seen a 391% rise in six months. We have seen a
% rise in a year and
friends, 3841% rise in five years.
So, this stock is definitely in a positive momentum.
Of course, it is volatile,
but at the same time, the fundamentals are
strong.  Because of this,
this stock has given us a good momentum,
this stock has
given us good returns, so first of all,
friends, let's discuss its quarterly results a
little bit. So, the
quarterly results, friends, are very good
and very good, so look here,
now the results of the December quarter have been
declared here,
let's discuss a little bit. So,
you can see here, friends,
in the December quarter,
friends, sales have been made, sales of 6161 crores have been made, compared
to the previous quarter, friends,
we have seen sales increasing in this quarter. Now, let's see
what happens from here on. The insurance sector, friends, is what the
last quarter is,
okay, the March quarter, there are
more insurance companies in it, friends,
what do they do on a larger scale, friends, they do sales, okay,
so this stock can go up even more, friends,
now look at the expenses, friends.
Expenses were 5199 crores. Operating profit,
friends, is 962 crores. We see
a better operating profit here than the previous quarter.
Now,
if we consider the net profit, friends, the net profit
was 724 crores and in the previous quarter it was
694 crores. That is, the net
profit has increased.
In the previous quarter, there was a profit of 580 crores. Friends, this means that
this stock has shown a good profit growth quarter on quarter. That is,
fundamentally, friends. And
if you look at the revenue-wise, we see that the stock has
given a good performance here.
And
if you consider the price-to-earnings ratio, friends, the
price-to-
earnings ratio is only 38. And if you
consider the market capitalization, there is a
market capitalization of 96,000 crores. 500, 96,500 crores.
That is, according to PE, if  If we look at it, is the
stock available at a good
valuation? Okay, so
fundamentally, if we look at it, the valuation is
currently good in line with the PE.
Let us now
discuss, friends,
what are the next targets we can get in this stock
and
what kind of returns we can get here after buying at the current level.
But
before that, friends, if you look at the sales
growth, profit growth and CHR growth, it is
very good. In five
years, friends, there is a
profit share growth of 13 percent. 13% profit
growth is in five years and 8%
friends, CAGR growth is
shown by this stock in the last five
years. That is, there is a good growth. Now,
friends, this stock is
not showing much momentum. But one good thing
about it is that whatever momentum there is in it, whatever
growth there is, it is
a continuous growth.  It is
not that the stock is
very volatile, friends. In a
good way, friends, even if this
stock comes down a little, it shows a good downside, but
what this stock does is bounce back in a
good way and
tries to show us new targets on the upside. So definitely, if you
look at it in the long term,
this stock has had a good performance and
this performance can continue to be good
because look at insurance companies,
friends, generally their expenses are
low, friends, okay, and whatever
claims come, they come very rarely, that is,
if you collect 100 rupees from the market, then
what they have to do here through claims is that they have to share two to three rupees. It is
not that much.
Even if you have to share 10-20 rupees,
friends,
you still have 80 rupees. Okay, so this is a
good business. This is a business with a good margin.
And most importantly, the company is
completely debt-free. You
can see that there is zero debt on the company.
What are the reserves of 13000 crores,
friends? If you look at it, the
company has a very good fundamental. Now,
friends, let's think whether we should
buy this stock above the current level.
So, friends, look, a very good
pattern is forming here.
An ascending triangle pattern has been broken out. After the
breakout,
this stock has made a good momentum.
You can see how good momentum this stock has
made here. I will
try to show you percentage wise.
After the breakout, this stock has made an average of 30%
momentum and again.
Generally, if you look at it, any
stock that has shown a fall has
shown an average of 30% fall again.
Of course, this fall was expected because the
market as a whole had turned negative, friends,
so this fall was
expected. But now, if you look at it, if
you have technical
knowledge and if you have been a follower on your channel
since the beginning, you will
know that you
All the patterns that are there are covered
and now what is happening in this pattern friends,
this has taken a good bounce back,
which
was the support level for this, okay, in my opinion,
whatever the support level was, it was Rs 1746,
from there the stock has taken a good bounce
back. A hammer type candle has been
formed here, a dragon fly
doji or you can also call it a hammer candle,
okay, such a type of
candle has been formed by this which
shows us a huge buying here,
above the support level, so a good buying has come here
and now due to the quarterly results,
we are also seeing a good upside here,
so definitely,
friends, in the coming days,
we can see good targets here.
Now let's discuss how to see the targets,
who can be seen.
So friends,
first of all, if we see the pattern here,
then a pattern here, friends.  What
we see forming is a
W pattern or a double bottom
pattern. If a double bottom pattern
breaks out here, friends, then as many targets as there are targets,
friends, the neck line is OK, friends, whatever its
low is,
friends, there are as many targets as there are. What
we see on the
upside is 1164%
targets, friends, so on the upside
too, friends, generally, what
we see is a
₹232 target, that is, targets up to ₹2230.
We
can see these stocks in these stocks. On the upside, these
targets can
definitely be achieved in the coming days, friends. Even if you are a long-term
investor,
what can you do with this stock? Friends, you
can include it in your portfolio.
This is a good stock, but again, this is a
buying recommendation.
Now, friends, there is one more thing
that the stock is on the daily time frame.  It has
come around 200 MA,
so friends, this is also an
important support level and from there
this stock is trying to bounce back
and now friends, the next three
months are going to be very important for this stock
because these
last three months, okay, this is the
March quarter, there is a lot of
pressure on the insurance company to sell insurance,
okay, because in this quarter, the
salesmen, friends, they are
trying to sell a lot of insurance,
it has a
big impact on the profitability here and the
results of the next quarter,
friends, they are going to be better than this,
so we are going to see a good momentum in the stock.
So friends, generally, I
think that the targets are for a
target of Rs 232, that is,
for a target of Rs 2230, you
can buy this stock, friends, and even if
this stock goes down, you
can still hold that stock, friends.  Because it
is a fundamentally strong company, sometimes it
can give you a good profit here. So friends,
remember this, there is no buying recommendation.
I am making this video only for analysis purposes. So I hope you liked this video.
If you liked the video, like the video, share it,
subscribe to the channel. See you in the next video.
Until then, good bye, take care and have a good time.
Thank you very much to all of you.